你应该已经把TextView组件更换成ListView组件
You should have changed the TextView into a ListView element.
然后你就可以删除文本属性  因为你已经不再需要它了
Then you can remove this text attribute because you don't need it anymore.
想一下之前的产品设计图  你应该记得这个天气预报列表占据了整个屏幕
Now from the UX mocks, you'll remember that the list takes up the whole screen,
我们这里设置宽高值都为  match_parent  跟父视图大小一致
so we want to set the width and height to be match_parent. That will make
这会让我们的这个ListView组件匹配其父视图的尺寸  也就是RelativeLayout布局
the ListView match the dimensions of its parent, which is this RelativeLayout.
RelativeLayout的宽高也是match_parent  我们找找它的父类
And to find out the parent of this RelativeLayout, it's actually in this
当然要在activity_main.xml这个文件里找  因为Activity是被这个Fragment布局填充的
activity_main XML file because the fragment is contained within the activity.
在这个文件里  我们看到这个视图的宽高同样是match_parent
Within this file, we see that this view is also match_parent for height and
所以我们现在就可以确认这个ListView组件一定是全屏显示了
width. So now we can confirm that the ListView actually will take up
回到fragment_main.xml这个文件  我们可以为ListView组件
the full screen. Going back to the fragment_main file, we can add the id,
添加一个名为listview_forecast的id  然后  因为这个布局只包含一个子类
listview_forecast, onto the ListView. And then, since this layout only contains
所以我们可以把RelativeLayout改成FrameLayout咯
one child, we can simplify the layout by changing this into a FrameLayout.